The search will continue,
but let's suspend it for now.
It's quite obvious.
We must let it decide its own course.
I'll observe it first,
then combine it with JoJo Kujo's memories
for everyone to find out the real truth!
This weird little fruit baby probably
absorbed the bone when it was germinating.
And Palesnake is here somewhere inside
this prison to find out what's behind this.
What will come out of this pod?
He's here because he wants to know
what begins when it's finally born.
You have to go find the main body.
And when you do, blow him off the map.
You son of a bitch!
This is way worse than I imagined!
That disgusting troll hit my face with
his foul poisonous drool before I knew it!
Now my mouth is half gone, slowly.
Little or little.
What should I do?
Should I go after Jolene's boat? No!
The plan was to go find that
Stan's user and assassinate him,
so goddammit I'm sticking to it!
It's the only way it gets done.
I don't wanna play.
Let's go outside.
Let's go, go.
1, 2, 3.
Come and find a way.
I'm lonely.
I'm a person who is me.
Step to the top.
Break out,
Break out, don't worry.
This might be a silly question, but
why'd you make him stop the boat here?
Now, quick, turn off the
engine, and keep quiet.
Listen, do you hear something?
Hey, I told you to turn off the engine!
Now hurry up, buffoon!
Abnormal conditions traced in
all disciplined cell zones.
Security now set to level
four in its entire complex.
Alertness is at max priority.
A 12.7 millimeter heavy machine gun.
Operational distance range
is 1,000 to 2,000 meters.
If we were barely grazed
by one of those bullets,
both our limbs and this
boat would be shattered.
Hey, quiet down, will you?
You're making waves, they'll see us.
You'll break the steering wheel.
Get away from it!
Just stay calm.
If they knew we were here, there
would already be a hail of gunfire.
At 210!
I just saw a ripple in
the water by that grove!
Maybe it's a fish or Cutter.
Oh, crap.
They're headed right to us!
Excuse me, if you take these leaves, Master,
you'll be able to make a... You idiot!
I told you to keep your trap shut!
Wait, please, you don't understand, sir.
Take this frond and fold it in half.
You weave the leaflets, then
you place it up against here.
You then secure it with a stock.
Take the sap and smear it on your face.
There we go.
Now everybody's ready
for the plan, together.
Emergency!
All units back to the
Discipline Cell Ward now!
I repeat, abort and return!
We have to go back.
This isn't standard protocol.
Must be pretty serious.
Well, you heard him.
Wait!
Holy shit, it's them!
They saw us.
Start the engine up and let's go.
Hurry!
There's not enough time!
We'll be dead before it even spins!
What kind of crap did you pull of
the discipline cells, scumbags!
Don't move!
Stay right where we can see you.
Get down in the ground and
don't try anything funny.
Hey, you giant freak!
Do you wanna get shot?
Get on your knees!
Hey, the boat!
Don't worry, we can borrow one of theirs.
And by we, I mean you.
What the hell was that just now?
We'll be taking this boat.
Get back safely.
The crocodiles are hungry,
so try not to get eaten.
Time for a drive! No!
Jolene, are you okay with plants?
Let's keep heading towards the east.
The sun's getting low, we'd better hurry.
They're so brutal, treating
me like a base object.
I like it.
Jolene, may I ask you
to stop that whistling?
I find it highly irksome.
Besides,
those guards might come after us, and I
want to keep an ear out for their engines.
What is it?
Jolene, may I ask you
to stop that whistling?
I find it highly irksome.
No, my voice is gone!
I am...
This guy...
Stealing the green child and escaping
with it wasn't his only goal here!
He was secretly attacking us!
Are you feeling alright?
Your breathing is very
erratic and shallow.
So is mine, Jolene.
Do you feel my rapid heartbeat
suddenly being so close?
Now do you fully understand
my feelings for you?
Not my eyes my tongue look are you
telling me you can't find any words?
I understand that feeling
all too well but words
are unnecessary see i
feel the exact same way.
You want to kiss me
don't you how about the
type where our tongues
join in sultry tango?
When and how did that
creature attack us i didn't
even notice we clearly need
to watch him every second?
I'm confused help me out
here do you want to kiss or
not or is this an indication
that you're partial to more
unorthodox proclivities do
you prefer to kiss like a
contortionist he's an automatic
pursuit style stand he?
He obediently follows
orders like a slave and
grovels at your feet to
seem harmless and pathetic.
Obviously, that's his
effed-up little trick.
He's a stand that specifically waits for
the moments when we're most off guard.
Then he strikes automatically.
We'll both be dead if
we don't do something.
Okay, my back is turned now.
Try attacking me.
I need Anastasia to notice.
Yeah, yeah, ma.
That is my name and don't you forget it.
Here's what happens when
you lick a frog's skin.
You make a gooey liquid made of a delicious
combination of lard, blood, and brains.
Then rub it all over your
skin, your entire body.
It's a wonderful beauty secret.
It gives you superior hydration.
If you desire, I can catch 10 more and
make you a miniskirt out of the skin.
And if you don't mind me saying so, I
would be incredibly honored to do it.
I'll make your legs look
very long and slender,
your calves shapely and your butt perky.
Jolene, tell me if
there's something wrong.
Seriously.
If a trigger is really necessary here,
then it makes sense that there'd
be a trigger to his attacks.
What's worse, if they're
launched automatically.
Exactly what I was waiting for.
I stretched my thread over my skin
and waited for something to touch it.
When I look away, that's when
the automatic attack starts.
That's his power.
Hitting at your weakest point.
But also, I figured out
a sneaky ass method.
Mosquitos.
Jolene, what's happening to you?
Jolene!
Wait, was I wrong about this?
It's not only mosquitoes.
Shit, he's obviously got other ways to
hit us besides those blood-sucking bugs.
You bastard, what did you do?
Tell me, Master.
It's up to you.
Should I continue driving
us back to supposed safety?
Or maybe you prefer to fight with me.
One-on-one, as the expression goes.
Or would you like to run?
I was right.
The mosquitoes are just part of it.
But what the hell else
is he going to let loose?
Come on, come on!
He's doing something horrible
to us that we can't even see!
Run away!
You might like to know.
I believe this is the very last
chance you have to run away.
Prepare yourself, wretch.
Prepare yourself for your
single greatest regret,
that you were shat out into this world.
Go to the back of the boat,
in the port side corner.
Move it.
Now take out everything you've been hiding
from us I want you to lay it out on my
feet and show me no funny business okay I
have two beetles there's
also a karaoke mic
packets of sugar substitute and these
three frogs I also have a raw frog skin one
head of broccoli and
four mock strawberries
and two used matches and that's everything
I promise you it's not as creepy stuff
we're upwind of him but something is still
attacking us what the hell is it though
so you embody an automatic pursuit stand
then which means whatever your attack
target is it has to be fixed you are correct
it's completely fixed ever since I first
touched Jolene Cujo
well you know the answer
So with Jolene as the target,
you were ordered by your
user not to run away,
or in fact do anything else,
until she's been killed.
Ya Ya Ma.
And if you're planning
to stay by her side,
I think there's something
you should know, Master.
That would leave me with no other
choice but to finish you off, too.
Wait, is it a spit?
Ya Ya Ma, do you still not understand?
There's no way you can destroy or stop me.
I'm afraid you'll have
to get used to the idea
There was only ever one way either of
you were going to survive this trip,
and that was to escape me.
Alas you have failed
I think we're gonna have
to stop this boat and fast.
All that foamy spray flying up
if he's mixed his nasty saliva?
He used to attack us before
with the marsh water.
We're now getting splashed
with we are screwed
All right, stand up and get
your ass in the driver's seat
Make the boat go faster, move.
You hear me? Come on, get up.
No, no, it's the opposite.
Higher speed creates more spray.
If you do that, we'll melt
like hot wax in minutes.
Yes, most certainly, Master.
I will do precisely as you have asked me.
Huh?
Jolene, it seems like he's
no longer attacking us,
despite the fact that he
clearly hasn't sped up the boat.
Ya, ya, ma.
S-something's not right.
Ah!
Dixus birds! Hide! Hide! Freak!
Dive or drive,
it doesn't matter what his attack methods
are, we don't have to worry anymore.
Since this scaly, wretched freak is
a perfect automatic pursuit stand,
I simply implanted a frog into
his brain and subsequently
attached its brain right
to his pursuit sensor.
Therefore, just like a frog,
he'll be in perpetual pursuit.
Ah.
Um, uh-oh.
What am I supposed to do again?
I can't remember.
Oh, yes!
I am an automatic pursuer.
I've been ordered to kill Jolene Cujo
and abscond with the Green Child.
I know that much.
I don't have time for this!
I've been derailed!
I have to disseminate my spit
spray and attack Anastasia.
I'll rub some plastic onto the
propellers to create static electricity,
and its resistance will
scatter my spitflex everywhere.
He can try, but he'll
never figure this one out.
But I can't get past my fear of the birds!
Gotta hide!
Must get away from them!
No, I wet myself, just like a frog!
Wow, so cute!
What a beautiful body that is!
Come here, I have to catch you!
I have to catch you!
Ooh, a beetle!
I believe it's safe to
leave him alone now.
Now, we need to get back
to FF and heal your wounds.
But before that, we must wait for
them to take out D &G and return.
What the hell?
I've seen crazy shit in
here, but nothing like this.
Where did the guards and prisoners go?
They're just gone.
It's only been 10 minutes.
And what are these?
Are there actual trees growing
in here all of a sudden?
How are we supposed to report this?
And what's the deal with him?
Can he not talk or what?
He's prisoner number ME14067.
He goes by D &G.
His forearm is just blood and bone now.
It's hanging by a thread.
He's in no shape for questioning.
You've got some balls sending in
a gross creepy stand like that.
So is payback.
Here's some FF ammo for your head.
Hey I know that guy he's
father poochie the prison
chaplain did they bring him
here for that bastard's last
rites don't worry about him
just focus the most important
thing right now is making
sure D &G is dead as dirt.
359, 367, 373,
379, 383, 389, 397.
The 300s are done, now the 400s.
Starting with 401, 409.
Since D &G is injured to within a mere
hair's breadth of bleeding to death,
that can only mean that somewhere,
Jolene Cujoh is still alive.
And the massive amount of those
withered and rotting plant remains,
I surmise, must be due to the
presence of Dio's bone buried within.
Truly, Dio's bone employed the prisoners'
bodies to instigate a movement
that's beyond my imagination.
Simply magnificent.
We should celebrate that
this has finally begun.
For 22 years, I have awaited this moment.
Anything and everything D &G saw here,
I have to pull out of the
man himself while I can.
Well, well, Survivors Guccio.
Though it seems you were
witness to none of the action,
I still believe something special
was born from all those plans.
Wouldn't you agree that
birthed Voren's rejoicing?
And that will soon belong to me.
Do you want to know the
definition of true happiness?
When you hold heaven in your hands.
We must praise what has been born unto us.
It is heaven embodied.
A new world has opened up and I am
going to be at the vanguard of it!
Wonderful!
Give due praise to this deep emotion!
Ah, Handel's exquisite messiah!
A time-honored masterpiece!
piece.
How fitting.
A perfect piece.
As if the sounds themselves were aglow.
It's often said that Handel
continued to play this
his own magnum opus until
the day before his death.
Right.
We're gonna leave D &G to the medics
and question them after treatment.
All the rest of us are gonna
search for the prisoners and
guards to see where in the
hell they could We're to God!
Let's go! Yes, sir.
Well, in that case, I'm going to
question him before his treatment.
Losing sight of that newly born miracle
would make me very, very unhappy.
Okay, let's back it out! Got it.
That face!
I recognize the face
hiding under that hat!
Eat this, pal! You should know,
users with automatic pursuit stands are
defenseless when under counterattack.
That's just the risk you take!
Yes, I was right! FF!
Why is she at this Discipline Cell?
And how long? Not good!
She's going after TNG!
It's a disk!
Pale Snake is here somewhere.
Shit, where is he?
Which direction did he
throw that damn disk from?
479.
487.
491.
499.
No way!
He's who threw it?
Monster!
Troublesome.
This is troublesome indeed.
If you're currently here planning
to unceremoniously eliminate D &G,
then that must mean his stand, Yayama,
is simultaneously after
Jolene's life, correct?
It's him.
This can't be happening.
How fortuitous.
I have something to ask him myself.
His death would be quite
problematic, you see.
Are you trying to tell me
that Pale Snake is really...
Ah, so what are you going to do if I am?
Will I then immediately
become top priority?
Or will finishing off D &G still
take precedence over me? I knew it.
Your father Poochie!
You bastard!
Although you think I cold.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do.
In my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today.
Thank you.